yescustom.com 2015-04-01

# Privacy Policy

Customdropshipping is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers and all visitors to our website. We have instituted the following policies and procedures to ensure that your privacy is respected. By visiting Customdropshipping  you agree to the policies stated below:

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally revise our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services and following customer feedback. When any changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this page. If there are changes of production in this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by promptly posting a notice on our site, or by sending you a notification to the email address you have registered on our site. We recommend that you regularly review this Privacy Policy for any updates or changes.

**What Information do we collect?**

You may browse the site without letting us know who you are or reveal any information about yourself. Once you register on the site you are no longer anonymous to us. When you place an order, we ask you to provide personal information such as name, e-mail address, billing address, telephone number, shipping address and so forth. If you are ordering for the first time we will also require you to choose a username and password so that we can create your account. When you sell artwork on Customdropshipping .com we may also ask for your PayPal account so that we may pay your commission for any items sold. Finally, we also maintain a history of the products you have ordered. All of the information that is gained through this process may be used by Customdropshipping, as well as providers of related services, in order to process your transaction.

We may also collect information about the pages you visit, the links you click, access to our website, referring websites and action taken in connection with the Customdropshipping  website or services. 

When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mails from Customdropshipping, we may use web beacons, customized links or similar technology to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you clicked on in order to provide more focused email communication and other information.

**How do we use your Personal Information?**

We collect your personal information to carry out the transactions that you have requested. Our goal is to provide you with a safe and efficient experience on our site. We may also use your information to provide you with more effective customer service, customize, measure, and improve our products, services, and technology or to communicate with you. Further, we may send mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We occasionally also send you product surveys or promotional mails to inform you of other products or services that are available from Customdropshipping .com.

**Will we share your Personal Information?**

Customdropshipping will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent. We will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to outside parties. Customdropshipping may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with the law (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of Customdropshipping .com and our users.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited service on our behalf, such as handling the processing of delivery of mails, provide customer support, host websites, process transactions, or perform statistical analysis of our services. These companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

**How do we protect your Personal Information?**

Customdropshipping is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the sensitive information that you input.

Passwords are used to help protect your account and personal information, so it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share your password with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving the site to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**How do I change or update my Account Information?**

You may view and edit your personal information online. In order to prevent information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your email address and password. After signing in, go to the Account Info or Earnings tab to update your information.

**How do you change your Communication Preferences?**

You can avoid future promotional emails from our site and services by following the specific instructions in the email you receive. You may also sign into your account and select the option to opt out on the Account Info tab.

**Children's Policy**

Customdropshipping is intended for users aged 13 or older. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of 13. Any information that we know is from a child under the age of 13 will be promptly deleted. Those under the age of 13 may only use Customdropshipping .com with permission and supervision of a parent or legal guardian. Your parent or guardian may request that we delete any personal information in our database and/or opt out of receiving any communication.

**Do we use Cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a webpage server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Customdropshipping  uses cookies to store information that uniquely identifies our users and secures their personal information. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify this in your browser settings if you prefer to decline cookies.

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at [order.yescustom@yahoo.com](mailto:order.yescustom@yahoo.com) .We welcome your comments regarding our Privacy Policy. If you have questions or comments, please feel free to e-mail us at [order.yescustom@yahoo.com](mailto:order.yescustom@yahoo.com).
